<dashboard hideExport="true" hideEdit="true">
  <label>ITOps - Triage - Notable Events</label>
  <row id="main">
    <panel>
      <html>
      <div class="overview">
A notable event is the foundational unit of the IT Service Intelligence (ITSI) Event Analytics functionality. A notable event is a stored alert with a unique ID, time, status, severity, and owner. Notable events are typically generated by a correlation search, but they can also be directly fed into the system by anomaly detection or other REST sources. Notable events are fed into the Event Analytics Rules Engine to create episodes and trigger episode actions.
      </div>
      <div class="platform">
        <span class="bold">Platform: </span>
        <span>
<a target="_blank" href="https://www.splunk.com/en_us/software/splunk-enterprise.html">Splunk Enterprise</a>, 
<a target="_blank" href="https://www.splunk.com/en_us/software/it-essentials.html">Splunk IT Essentials</a>, 
<a target="_blank" href="https://www.splunk.com/en_us/software/it-service-intelligence.html">Splunk IT Service Intelligence</a>
         </span>
      </div>
      <div class="related">
        <span class="bold">Related: </span>
<span><a href="/app/$env:app$/itops__investigate__incidents">Incidents</a>, </span>
<span><a href="/app/$env:app$/itops__triage__alerts">Alerts</a>, </span>
<span><a href="/app/$env:app$/itops__triage__tickets">Tickets</a></span>
      </div>
      <div class="basics">
        <h1>The Basics</h1>
        <p>
ITSI Event Analytics is designed to make event storms manageable and actionable. After data is ingested into ITSI from multiple data sources, it's processed through correlation searches to create notable events. ITSI generates notable events when a correlation search or multi-KPI alert meets specific conditions that you define. Notable event aggregation policies group the events into meaningful episodes, a group of events occurring as part of a larger sequence (an incident or period considered in isolation). Use Episode Review to view episode details and identify issues that might impact the performance and availability of your IT services. You can then take actions on the episodes, such as running a script, pinging a host, or creating tickets in external systems.
        </p>
      </div>
      <div class="help">
        <h1>Help, Guidance, and More Information</h1>
        <ul>
          <li>
              <a target="_blank" href="https://docs.splunk.com/Documentation/ITSI/latest/EA/AboutCS">Overview of correlation searches in ITSI - Documentation</a>
          </li>
          <li>
              <a target="_blank" href="https://docs.splunk.com/Documentation/ITSI/latest/EA/NotableEvents">Overview of notable events in ITSI - Documentation</a>
          </li>
          <li>
              <a target="_blank" href="https://docs.splunk.com/Documentation/ITSI/latest/EA/UseSDK">Use the Notable Event Actions SDK - Documentation</a>
          </li>
          <li>
              <a target="_blank" href="https://conf.splunk.com/watch/conf-online.html?search=notable%20events&amp;search.products=option_1584675302134&amp;search.products=1601591781565001Na8P&amp;search.products=1518807815929006Tats&amp;search.products=1554416734780001tYXj">Splunk .conf Online</a>
          </li>
        </ul>
      </div>
    </html>
    </panel>
    <panel><html></html></panel>
  </row>
</dashboard>